[{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":15223,"timeElapsed":132111},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":17835,"timeElapsed":149948},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":15889,"timeElapsed":165840},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7653,"timeElapsed":173495},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679271153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7041,"timeElapsed":180537},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679279866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":8712,"timeElapsed":189250},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7115,"timeElapsed":196367},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":18705,"timeElapsed":215074},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8727,"timeElapsed":223804},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679331069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":13779,"timeElapsed":240453},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":7424,"timeElapsed":247879},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679344880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6383,"timeElapsed":254264},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679379468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":34587,"timeElapsed":288852},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679388287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8817,"timeElapsed":297671},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":16217,"timeElapsed":313890},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679422269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":17761,"timeElapsed":331653},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679429986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7715,"timeElapsed":339370},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679435551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5563,"timeElapsed":344935},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679455564,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20012,"timeElapsed":364948},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679464744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6073,"timeElapsed":374128},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679469614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4868,"timeElapsed":378998},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679478287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8670,"timeElapsed":387671},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":11769,"timeElapsed":399440},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679494616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4559,"timeElapsed":403999},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679501420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6804,"timeElapsed":410804},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679507789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6368,"timeElapsed":417173},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679512268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4477,"timeElapsed":421651},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679516727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4456,"timeElapsed":426111},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679522252,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5523,"timeElapsed":431636},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679532579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5623,"timeElapsed":441963},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679537959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5379,"timeElapsed":447343},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679544253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6293,"timeElapsed":453637},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679585494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":41237,"timeElapsed":494877},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679596536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":11042,"timeElapsed":505920},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679601211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4673,"timeElapsed":510595},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679605413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4200,"timeElapsed":514797},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5354,"timeElapsed":520153},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679614478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3706,"timeElapsed":523862},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":13666,"timeElapsed":539498},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679633970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3855,"timeElapsed":543354},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679639499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5528,"timeElapsed":548883},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679646884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7384,"timeElapsed":556268},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679650704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3819,"timeElapsed":560088},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679654308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3603,"timeElapsed":563692},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679658039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":567423},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679661564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3522,"timeElapsed":570948},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679665008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3443,"timeElapsed":574392},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679676989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9542,"timeElapsed":586373},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679696091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":19100,"timeElapsed":605475},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679700392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":609776},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5102,"timeElapsed":614879},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679709542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4044,"timeElapsed":618926},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679713199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3656,"timeElapsed":622582},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679718677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5476,"timeElapsed":628061},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679728825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":10146,"timeElapsed":638209},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679735813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":6987,"timeElapsed":645197},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679751224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":12712,"timeElapsed":660608},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679769337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":18111,"timeElapsed":678721},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679776549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7211,"timeElapsed":685933},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679791557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":15007,"timeElapsed":700941},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679806946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":15387,"timeElapsed":716330},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679815693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8746,"timeElapsed":725077},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679823891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8196,"timeElapsed":733275},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679836490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12598,"timeElapsed":745874},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679850175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":13685,"timeElapsed":759559},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679862233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8335,"timeElapsed":771617},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679868177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5942,"timeElapsed":777561},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679871940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3762,"timeElapsed":781324},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679880635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8694,"timeElapsed":790019},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679897237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":16600,"timeElapsed":806621},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679902100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4862,"timeElapsed":811484},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679907818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5716,"timeElapsed":817201},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679916391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8572,"timeElapsed":825775},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679926981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":10589,"timeElapsed":836365},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679935000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5243,"timeElapsed":844384},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679937934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2932,"timeElapsed":847318},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679941560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3624,"timeElapsed":850944},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679945600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4040,"timeElapsed":854984},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679949399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":858783},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679952701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3301,"timeElapsed":862085},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679956204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3501,"timeElapsed":865588},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679959250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3045,"timeElapsed":868634},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679962054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":871438},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679968711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":878095},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679971677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2965,"timeElapsed":881061},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679974934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3256,"timeElapsed":884318},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679978328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3392,"timeElapsed":887712},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679981599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3269,"timeElapsed":890983},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679984625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3026,"timeElapsed":894009},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679988668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4040,"timeElapsed":898052},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679991878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3210,"timeElapsed":901262},{"subjectID":"48xe4vdjnl","prolificID":"67700ec907815f27b6070f01","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745bbf5bf4e5272806fe96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679995402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3522,"timeElapsed":904786}]